Guide to the Lois Milner collection of broadcast radio audio recordings 1940-1952
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
- Milner Discs, 1940-1952
  - 1947 Septemer-1949 October, Compact disc (Disc 102)
    - Children's Friend – The Place, 2899A Children's Friend "The Nativity" 2, 1948 January 3; 1947 December 20 (Track 323)
    - 2294A Children's Friend – Queenie Who Wanted To Dance, (Not finished due to record damage), Children's Friend – Hugh And His Daisy, 1947 September 6; 1947 September 13 (Track 334)
  - 1946 June-1947 May, Compact disc (Disc 103)
    - Children's Friend – Papa Bear Loses His Sock, 1947 May 3 (Track 335)
    - 1096A Children's Friend of the Air "Little Liza Honey Bee", 1096B Children's Friend of the Air – Skee Gee Pinky Rabbit, 1946 June 29; 1946 August 17 (Track 336)
    - 1382B Children's Friend of the Air "The Old Woman in the Shoe", 1382A, 1946 September 21, undated (Track 337)
  - 1946 September-1948 August, Compact disc (Disc 104)
    - 1382B Children's Friend of the Air "The Old Woman in the Shoe", 1382A, 1946 September 21, undated (Track 337)
    - 3601B Children's Friend of the Air – Gooseberry Pie, 3601A Morton Downey, 1948 August 14; 1948 July 22 (Track 338)
    - Point With Pride Part I, Point With Pride Part II, Undated (Track 339)
  - 1947 July-1951 March, Compact disc (Disc 105)
    - Point With Pride Part I, Point With Pride Part II, Undated (Track 339)
    - Children's Friend of the Air – Friend of the Wilderness, Unknown, 1947 July 21, undated (Track 340)
    - This Is Your PTA – Mr. Cannon, Mrs. Jacobs – "Drama on Safety", Mind Your Manners – 173rd Meeting – Children's Radio Program Part 1 Closed Circuit from NBC – Not to be aired, 1951 March 21, undated (Track 341)
  - 1949 April-1951 March, Compact disc (Disc 106)
    - This Is Your PTA – Teenagers "What 2 Like in a Parent", 1951 March 27 (Track 342)
    - UNESCO 6 "Was He Black, Was He White" for PTA Program, 1949 April 13 (Track 343)
    - This Is Your PTA – Mr. Williams, Hal, Marty – Teenage Drivers, This Is Your PTA – Elaine Cannon, J. Edgar Lyon, Mrs. J. Fisher – Parent Teacher Problems, 1951 January 15; 1951 February 13 (Track 344)
  - 1944 January-1951 April, Compact disc (Disc 107)
    - 6357 You and Your PTA – Mae Rose, Emil Nyman – Safety and Drama in School, Mind Your Manners – 173rd Meeting – Children's Radio Program Part 2, February 20, undated (Track 345)
    - This Is Your PTA – Dr. Brown Mortenson – Panel on Parenthood, Mind Your Manners – 175th Meeting – Children's Radio Program Part 1, 1951 April 10, undated (Track 346)
    - 2569A Women's Council (Broken Record), 2569B Point With Pride Safety Program (Broken Record), 1944 January 15; 1944 February 19 (Track 347)
    - You and Your PTA – Was He Black Was He White (2/27/51), Fibber McGee and Molly - Comedy Drama - Sego Milk, 1951 February 27, undated (Track 348)
  - 1948 March-1951 February, Compact disc (Disc 108)
    - You and Your PTA – Was He Black Was He White (2/27/51), Fibber McGee and Molly - Comedy Drama - Sego Milk, 1951 February 27, undated (Track 348)
    - This Is Your PTA – Walker, Thurman, Larson – Whitehouse Conference, 6179A This Is Your PTA – Dr. Lyman Bennion – Teenagers, January 8, undated (Track 349)
    - 3209B Children's Friend 1 Freedom Train, The Cost of Freedom, 3209A Miles – News of the World, 1948 March 20; 1948 March 19 (Track 350)
  - 1944 September-1949 May, Compact disc (Disc 109)
    - 3207A George C. Marshall for 10:30PM 2, 3207B Children's Friend 2 Freedom Train, The Cost of Freedom, Undated; 1948 March 20 (Track 351)
    - 2139A Children's Friend "The Indian Attack" (Damaged – Flaking), 1947 August 9 (Track 352)
    - 233B SLC Council of Women, 233A Atlantic Spotlight Part Two (Damaged – Broken), 1944 September 2; 1944 September 3 (Track 353)
    - Children's Friend of the Air "Mollies Mistake", Children's Friend "The Adventures of Meelo" – Orlan Rinder Story, 1947 February 8; 1947 July 12 (Track 354)
    - When the Siren Sounds, Utah Power and Light – Sorenson (2-13-45), Undated; 1945 February 13 (Track 355)
    - Children's Friend of the Air – The Rainbow Party (5-28-49), Children's Friend – Mother Goose's Health Program (5-21-49), 1949 May 28; 1949 May 21 (Track 356)
  - 1947 February-1949 October, Compact disc (Disc 110)
    - Children's Friend of the Air – The Rainbow Party, Children's Friend – Mother Goose's Health Program, 1949 May 28; 1949 May 21 (Track 356)
    - Children's Friend – Tuffy and the Stone Rabbit, Children's Friend – The Women in the Shoe, 1947 May 31, undated (Track 357)
    - Heart Throbs of the West – Early Miners in Utah, International News, Children's Friend – The Finest Collection, 1947 February 23, undated; 1949 October 22 (Track 358)
  - 1949 October-1950 April, Compact disc (Disc 111)
    - Children's Friend of the Air "Flash Flood" Larry and Lucille Jensen, Children's Friend of the Air – The Finest Collection (Scratching causes bad skipping), 1949 October 15; 1949 October 22 (Track 359)
    - 5750A Mindy Carson, Chickens Many of 'em Cackling – Closed Circuit, 1950 April 10, undated (Track 360)
    - Children's Friend – The First Xmas, The Heritage of Winfold Street – Drama Part 2, Undated (Track 361)
    - Valley Fun Finders 2, NBC – Talk, Undated (Track 362)
  - 1947 July-1952 March, Compact disc (Disc 112)
    - Valley Fun Finders 2, NBC – Talk, Undated (Track 362)
    - KDYL – Fibber and Molly (Sego Milk) Part 1A, You and Your PTA – Air Check, 1952 March 18; 1952 March 14 (Track 363)
    - Children's Friend "Eph Celebrates the 24th", International News, 1947 July 19, undated (Track 364)
  - 1947 January-1947 March, Compact disc (Disc 113)
    - 16148 Heart Throbs of the West – Pioneer Fashion (Bad sound quality), The Hour of Greens, 1947 March 9 (Track 365)
    - Heart Throbs of the West, Southernaires Part 1, 1947 January 19, undated (Track 366)
    - Heart Throbs of the West – Mormon Battalion (Hard to hear), Sentimental Journey – Aircheck Part 1 (Skips a lot), 1947 January 24 (Track 367)
  - 1946 June-1948 February, Compact disc (Disc 114)
    - Heart Throbs of the West – Mormon Battalion (Hard to hear), Sentimental Journey – Aircheck Part 1 (Skips a lot), 1947 January 24 (Track 367)
    - Heart Throbs of the West – Pioneer Dentistry (6/23/46), Al Pearce 2 (6-27-46), 1946 June 23; 1946 June 27 (Track 368)
    - 3090A Children's Friend of the Air – Love in the House, 3090B Children's Friend of the Air – Whistling Spring, 1948 February 21, undated (Track 369)
  - 1949 September-1952 March, Compact disc (Disc 115)
    - KDYL – Fibber and Molly (Sego) Part 1A, KDYL – You and Your PTA, 1952 March 4; 1952 March 12 (Track 370)
    - 4643 Children's Friend of the Air – Bonnie Pae "Sure-Fire Cure", Chicken Every Sunday starring Bill Burk and Harry Vonzell, 1949 September 3, undated (Track 371)
  - 1947 June-1948 June, Compact disc (Disc 116)
    - Children's Friend of the Air "Chocolate Charley", R.F.D. America II Filter 3, 1948 June 9, undated (Track 372)
    - Heart Throbs of the West – The Spirit of Immigration, Dark Venture Part 1, 1947 July 6; 1947 June 24 (Track 373)
  - 1949 September-1952 March, Compact disc (Disc 117)
    - Point With Pride, 1956A Business and War Information Part II, 1944 May 6; 1943 July 14 (Track 374)
    - The American Farmer Part 1 (Bad recording), Hall of Fame I Master (Bad recording), 1948 February 28; 1948 (Track 375)
  - 1946 June-1951 April, Compact disc (Disc 118)
    - 1068B Children's Friend of the Air – Adventure by Torchlight, A Symphony of Melody, 1946 June 18, undated (Track 376)
    - Children's Friend of the Air "The Pumpkin", World News, 1949 October 29, undated (Track 377)
    - 6456A Mind Your Manners 2, 6453 Kallenborn World News, 1951 April 21; 1951 April 20 (Track 378)
  - 1945 March-1951 April, Compact disc (Disc 119)
    - 6456A Mind Your Manners 2, 6453 Kallenborn World News, 1951 April 21; 1951 April 20 (Track 378)
    - 4422A Children's Friend Part II Birthday Party, Children's Friend – Jasper the Giant, 1949 June 11; 1949 June 18 (Track 379)
    - When Siren Sounds – Utah Accident and Health Club Program 3, When Siren Sounds – Utah Accident and Health Club Program 4, 1945 March 1; 1945 March 8 (Track 380)
  - 1945 March-1949 May, Compact disc (Disc 120)
    - When Siren Sounds – Utah Accident and Health Club Program 3, When Siren Sounds – Utah Accident and Health Club Program 4, 1945 March 1; 1945 March 8 (Track 380)
    - Children's Friend – The Somaleland Boy, Children's Friend – The Vacant Lot, 1949 May 14; 1949 May 7 (Track 381)
    - Children's Friend of the Air – Soap Box Derby, Children's Friend Wheat For Grandpa, 1948 April 3; 1947 April 17 (Track 382)
  - 1947 April-1951 May, Compact disc (Disc 121)
    - Children's Friend of the Air – Soap Box Derby, Children's Friend Wheat For Grandpa, 1948 April 3; 1947 April 17 (Track 382)
    - Children's Friend of the Air "Ski Foot the Rabbit", Children's Friend of the Air "Tenderfoot", 1951 April 14; 1951 April 7 (Track 383)
    - Children's Friend of the Air "Carl Calls", Children's Friend of the Air –Grandma June's Surprise Violets, 1951 May 19; 1951 May 26 (Track 384)
  - 1950 October-1951 May, Compact disc (Disc 122)
    - Children's Friend of the Air "Carl Calls", Children's Friend of the Air –Grandma June's Surprise Violets, 1951 May 19; 1951 May 26 (Track 384)
    - Children's Friend of the Air "Sissy Britches", News - Miles, 1950 October 21; 1950 October 20 (Track 385)
    - Children's Friend of the Air "A May Day" "Gingerbread Party", Children's Friend of the Air "Dearest Friend", 1951 April 28; 1951 May 12 (Track 386)
  - 1946 January-1951 May, Compact disc (Disc 123)
    - Children's Friend of the Air "A May Day" "Gingerbread Party", Children's Friend of the Air "Dearest Friend", 1951 April 28; 1951 May 12 (Track 386)
    - Static Relations – Carson, Collings, Pop Corn Sound Like Wagon, 1950 July 7, undated (Track 387)
    - 2 Ladies Organ "Utah We Love Thee" (Muffled Sound), James Able (?), 1947 January 2; 1946 January 1 (Track 388)
    - L.D.S. Primary Hospital Appeal 1 and 2, Closed Circuit, February 1 (Track 389)
  - 1949 November-1951 March, Compact disc (Disc 124)
    - Children's Friend – A Good American – Mabel Harman (Thanksgiving) (End not recorded due to skipping), Unknown Comedy Drama Show, 1949 November 19, undated (Track 390)
    - Children's Friend of the Air "Green Eggs", Children's Friend of the Air "Millie and the Wee Yellow Chick", 1951 March 24; 1951 March 31 (Track 391)
  - 1950 May-1950 August, Compact disc (Disc 125)
    - KDYL – Children's Friend of the Air – Mrs. Bunns Little Bread Truck, KDYL – Children's Friend of the Air – Roary the Lion Loses His Roar, 1950 August 26; 1950 August 5 (Track 392)
    - Children's Friend of the Air – The White Emperor, 5844A Miles, 1950 May 13; 1950 May 11 (Track 393)
  - 1946 August-1948 March, Compact disc (Disc 126)
    - 1851B Tom Tom Indian Mood, 1851A Worlds Great Novels 1, Undated; 1947 March 28 (Track 394)
    - Children's Friend of the Air "The Garden Part 1", Children's Friend of the Air "Jack and the Weatherman", 1946 August 3; 1946 July 27 (Track 395)
    - Children's Friend – Mr. Snowman Meets the Sun (Bad Skipping Didn't Finish Transfer), Children's Friend – Frisky Boastful Squirrel (Bad Skipping), 1948 March 13; 1948 March 6 (Track 396)
  - 1948 March-1952 April, Compact disc (Disc 127)
    - Children's Friend – Mr. Snowman Meets the Sun (Bad Skipping Didn't Finish Transfer), Children's Friend – Frisky Boastful Squirrel (Bad Skipping), 1948 March 13; 1948 March 6 (Track 396)
    - Children's Friend "Fireworks" (Skips Bad, Story Not Finished), Children's Friend "Older N …(?)" (Skips at End), 1948 July 3; 1948 June 26 (Track 397)
    - National Broadcasting Company Inc. – KDYL – Fibber and Molly Part 1A, KDYL - Your PTA "The Bennetts Talk It Over", 1952 April 22; 1952 April 23 (Track 398)
  - 1946 August-1947 November, Compact disc (Disc 128)
    - Children's Friend "An Indian Never Forgets Thanksgiving" Comedy, 1947 November 22 (Track 399)
    - 1305B Children's Friend "Oronto and Toronto", 1305A Children's Friend – Pancha De La Mancha, 1946 September 7; 1946 August 31 (Track 400)
  - 1951 December-1952 February, Compact disc (Disc 129)
    - 1086B Children's Friend of the Air "Peter Stands Pat", Unknown Program (Hard to hear, very grainy sound), July 13 (Track 401)
    - KDYL – Fibber and Molly Part 1A, You and Your PTA, 1951 December 11; 1951 December 12 (Track 402)
    - KDYL – Fibber and Molly Part 2B, KDYL – You and Your PTA, 1952 February; 1952 February 20 (Track 403)
  - 1951 February-1952 February, Compact disc (Disc 130)
    - KDYL – Fibber and Molly Part 2B, KDYL – You and Your PTA, 1952 February; 1952 February 20 (Track 403)
    - McGee and Molly Sego Milk Part 1A, You and Your PTA – Drama on Founder's Day, 1951 February 6 (Track 404)
    - This Is Your PTA – Drama: Who Me?, This Is Your PTA – "Tension in Parent Teacher Relations", 1951 October 31; 1951 November 7 (Track 405)
  - 1946 June-1951 November, Compact disc (Disc 131)
    - This Is Your PTA – Drama: Who Me?, This Is Your PTA – "Tension in Parent Teacher Relations", 1951 October 31; 1951 November 7 (Track 405)
    - This Is Your PTA – "Panel: Making Things in a Mechanical World", Fibber McGee and Molly, 1951 November 14, undated (Track 406)
    - Children's Friend of the Air – Sidney Goes Fishing, Sunday Morning Musical Moods (Skips), 1946 June 15, undated (Track 407)
  - 1946 June-1951 April, Compact disc (Disc 132)
    - Children's Friend of the Air – Sidney Goes Fishing, Sunday Morning Musical Moods (Skips), 1946 June 15, undated (Track 407)
    - This Is Your PTA "What I Like In A Teacher", Part 2, 1951 April 3 (Track 408)
    - 6436A This Is Your PTA – Dr. Crawley Earl Anderson, 1951 April 17 (Track 409)
    - Children's Friend of the Air – Beyond the City, 1957A Children's Friend of the Air "Buying Sunshine For Mother", 1947; 1947 May 10 (Track 410)
  - 1947 May-1951 November, Compact disc (Disc 133)
    - Children's Friend of the Air – Beyond the City, 1957A Children's Friend of the Air "Buying Sunshine For Mother", 1947; 1947 May 10 (Track 410)
    - 4429A Children's Friend Part I Long May It Wave, Children's Friend "Ricardos Paint Brush", 1949 July 2; 1949 (Track 411)
    - This Is Your PTA "Friends At the House", KDYL – This Is Your PTA, 1951 November 28; 1951 November 21 (Track 412)
  - 1947 March-1951 November, Compact disc (Disc 134)
    - This Is Your PTA "Friends At the House", KDYL – This Is Your PTA, 1951 November 28; 1951 November 21 (Track 412)
    - 1279A Children's Friend of the Air "Luni the Lion", 1279B Children's Friend of the Air "Secret At Hidden Valley", 1947 March 8; 1946 August 24 (Track 413)
    - 2107 Children's Friend of the Air – From Missouri, Children's Friend "The Prize Pumpkin", 1947 July 5; 1947 October 25 (Track 414)
  - 1946 June-1947 May, Compact disc (Disc 135)
    - 1567A KDYL – Children's Friend of the Air "Little Liza Honey Bee", Children's Friend of the Air "The Little Fairy Who Didn't Have A Mama", 1946 June 29; 1947 May 17 (Track 415)